SWETANK SUBHAM

MUZAFFARPUR, BIHAR, INDIA, 843103

+91 9110-09-0019 # SWETANKSUBHAM.R@GMAIL.COM # LINKEDIN.COM/IN/SWETANK-SUBHAM/ SWETANKSUBHAM.COM

Summary

I believe I am a good learner and describe myself as a lifelong learner and implementer. Very keen to use my technical and managing skills as well as learning for the betterment of software industry by keeping mutual growth in mind. I have corporate experience in software development and scripting which includes various web development projects in different technologies and frameworks like Django (Python), Laravel (PHP), Yii (PHP) and other frameworks like RASA (AI chatbot).

Skill Highlights

- Agile/Scrum methodology
- JavaScript
- Apache2 HTTP Server
- PHP
- Bash

- Python 3
- HTML 5/CSS 3
- MySQL
- Laravel
- Go Lang

- Django
- Linux
 - **RASA**
- Yii

Experience

Software Engineer – 07/2019 – Present

Great Software Laboratory, Pune

 Working as full-stack web developer. Role includes developing, managing, and deploying codes on web servers.

Software Engineer Intern – 08/2018 – 06/2019

Great Software Laboratory, Pune

Worked as full-stack web developer intern. Role was to develop browser-based web apps for the company.

Education

Bachelor of Technology

Computer Science and Engineering

(Graduation)

Lovely Professional University, Jalandhar, Punjab

2015 - 20198.05 CGPA

Nanodegree

Data Structures and Algorithms (Python)

(Udacity Certification)

Higher Secondary Certificate

(Intermediate/12th)

Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, English, Physical Education

Chandrasheel Vidyapeeth, Kanti, Muzaffarpur, Bihar

2012 - 201471.00 %

(Matric/10th)

Secondary School Certificate DAV Public School, Muzaffarpur, Bihar

2011 - 201210.00 CGPA